http://fileguru.com/privacy

BrainsBreaker Jigsaw Puzzles
RPM Remote Print Manager Elite...
Privacy Policy for FileGuru.com
The privacy of our visitors to FileGuru.com is important to us.
At FileGuru.com, we recognize that privacy of your personal information is important. Here is information on what types of personal information we receive and collect when you use visit FileGuru.com, and how we safeguard your information. We never sell your personal information to third parties.
Log Files. As with most other websites, we collect and use the data contained in log files. The information in the log files include your IP (internet protocol) address, your ISP (internet service provider, such as AOL or Shaw Cable), the browser you used to visit our site (such as Internet Explorer or Firefox), the time you visited our site and which pages you visited throughout our site.
Cookies and Web Beacons. We do use cookies to store information, such as your personal preferences when you visit our site. This could include only showing you a popup once in your visit, or the ability to login to some of our features, such as forums.
We use third party advertisements on FileGuru.com to support our site. Some of these advertisers may use technology such as cookies and web beacons when they advertise on our site, which will also send these advertisers information including your IP address, your ISP, the browser you used to visit our site, and in some cases, whether you have Flash installed. We also use Google Adsense to support our site. Ads provided by Google AdSense are targeted to be relevant to the content of the website and / or page they are on (i.e. they get the information from the website contents not the visitors themselves). Google Adsense uses cookies to serve ads on our site. Googleâ€™s use of DART cookies enables it to serve ads to the users based on their visit to the current site and to other sites on the Internet. A user may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting Google ad and content network privacy policy.
You can choose to disable or selectively turn off our cookies or third-party cookies in your browser settings, or by managing preferences in programs such as Norton Internet Security. However, this can affect how you are able to interact with our site as well as other websites. This could include the inability to login to services or programs, such as logging into forums or accounts.
Disclaimer
All the information published on the pages of FileGuru.com is the sole responsibility of a person/organization making the posting in the corresponding website category. Any questions, complaints or claims to the information provided should be directed to the appropriate Author or Company which has published the given information, not to the staff working for FileGuru.com.
Links to Other Websites
This site contains links to other sites. FileGuru.com is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Web sites. We encourage you to read the privacy statements of other web sites before disclosing any personal information on another site. These other sites may independently collect data, solicit personal information, or send their own cookies to you. The Company is not responsible for any use of the information including click-stream data that you may create when using such third party web sites. You should carefully review the privacy policies of these third party web sites in order to determine how they treat your personal information.
Contact us
If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, you can contact us.
